//Questions array
let questionBank = [{
        question: 'What is "...as hard as dragon scale and as light as a feather"?',
        answer: 'Mithril',
        answer_choices: ['Mithril', 'Adamantium', 'Titanuim', 'The Rock']
    },{
        question: "Who is Harry Potter's Defense Against The Dark Arts professor?",
        answer: 'Severus Snape',
        answer_choices: ['Albus Dumbledore', 'Dudley Dursley', 'Sirius Black', 'Severus Snape']
    },{
        question: 'What is the name of the story Bilbo wrote about his adventures?',
        answer: 'The Hobbit',
        answer_choices: ['The Hobbit', 'The Silmarillion', 'Hobbits Tale', 'Into the West']
    },{
        question: 'By what name do the Elves call Gandalf?',
        answer: 'Mithrandir',
        answer_choices: ['Mithrandir', 'Gandalf the Grey', 'Incanus', 'The Grey Pilgrim']
    },{
        question: 'What three swords were found in the Trolls Cave in The Hobbit?',
        answer: 'Orcrist, Sting and Glamdring',
        answer_choices: ['Orcrist, Sting and Glamdring', 'Narsil, Glamdring and Hadhafang', 'Sting, Anduil and The White Knife of Legolas', 'Aeglos, Orcrist and Sting']
    },{
        question: 'What is "...as hard as dragon scale and as light as a feather"?',
        answer: 'Mithril',
        answer_choices: ['Mithril', 'Adamantium', 'Titanuim', 'The Rock']
    },{
        question: 'Who is referred to as the Son of Glion?',
        answer: 'Gimli',
        answer_choices: ['Gimli', 'Durin', 'Balin', 'Legolas']
    },{
        question: '“Nine companions. So be it. You shall be the fellowship of the ring.” was said by who?',
        answer: 'Elrond',
        answer_choices: ['Elrond', 'Gandalf', 'Aragorn', 'Celeborn']
    },{
        question: 'How many Rings of Power were forged in the second age?',
        answer: '20',
        answer_choices: ['20', '9', '7', '1']
    },{
        question: 'What was Gollum’s hobbit name?',
        answer: 'Smeagol',
        answer_choices: ['Smeagol', 'Bandobras', 'Tom', 'Tobold']
    },{
        question: 'Who killed Martha and Thomas Wayne?',
        answer: 'Joe Chill',
        answer_choices: ['The Joker', 'Lucius Fox', 'Joe Chill', 'Alberto Falcone']
    },{
        question: "“I would have followed you, my brother...my captain...my king.” was said by who?",
        answer: 'Boromir',
        answer_choices: ['Aragorn', 'Legolas', 'Boromir', 'Pippin']
    },{
        question: 'Who paralyzed Barbara Gordon?',
        answer: 'The Joker',
        answer_choices: ['The Joker', 'Commisioner Gordon', 'Two Face', 'Bane']
    },{
        question: "What is the name of Wonder Woman's mother?",
        answer: 'Hyppolyta',
        answer_choices: ['Hyppolyta', 'Hera', 'Antiope', 'Persephone']
    },{
        question: "Who killed Superman?",
        answer: 'Doomsday',
        answer_choices: ['Lex Luthor', 'Doomsday', 'Darkseid', 'Stephenwolf']
    },{
        question: "Which villain discovered Batman's identity by deduction?",
        answer: 'Hugo Strange',
        answer_choices: ['Hugo Strange', 'The Riddler', 'The Joker', 'The Scarecrow']
    },{
        question: "What is Hermione's middle name?",
        answer: 'Jean',
        answer_choices: ['Rachel', 'Jean', 'Sarah', 'Haily']
    },{
        question: "How many names does Dumbledore have in his full name?",
        answer: '5',
        answer_choices: ['2', '4', '5', '6']
    },{
        question: "Who knocks out the troll in the ladies' bathroom in The Sorcerer's Stone?",
        answer: 'Ron',
        answer_choices: ['Harry', 'Professor Quirrell', 'Professor Snape', 'Ron']
    },{
        question: "Who decides where the children will be housed at Hogwarts?",
        answer: 'The Sorting Hat',
        answer_choices: ['The Sorting Hat', 'Dumbledore', 'The Sorting Broom', 'Hagrid']
    },{
        question: "What position does Harry play in Quidditch?",
        answer: 'Seeker',
        answer_choices: ['Seeker', 'Quaffle', 'Chaser', 'Sweeper']
    },

];
